Just departed from the sand port
Please arrest small vessels.
Armed Princess Baek San-ho and
Suspect in murder of Rep. Jang Jun-ik
Seo Moon-ju is riding
This is the Coast Guard.
stop the boat
The fleeing ship
stop the boat immediately
Please respond to the inquiry
This is the Republic of Korea Coast Guard.
Stop the boat immediately!
Uh, report the situation!
1 male
1 woman arrested
Ah...
Murder suspect Seo Moon-ju and
Baek San-ho, the armed princess,
Looks like you're not on board
Aww, Mr.
Block the surrounding roads
Please conduct a general inspection.
Mobilizing all possible manpower
Fly helicopters and drones
You must catch it
This is a matter of interest to the President.
yes, i understand
This is just news
Was a leading presidential candidate
Seo Moon-ju, New Republican Party candidate
About her husband, the late Congressman Jang Jun-ik.
Charged with murder and espionage
Known to be on the run
It's shocking
Please connect with the head of the National Intelligence Service.
yes
running away together
Bodyguard Baek San-ho
During the arrest process
About 20 bullets were fired.
Currently carrying a firearm
It is known that there is
Subject uses a vehicle
Trying to leave the area
likely
Checkpoint officers
Be aware of the fugitive's impressions
Inspect all vehicles thoroughly
I feel like I'm dreaming
Suddenly I become a murderer
Sanho becomes a military general...
What's next?
Meanwhile, the police
Special advisor on unification policy for the Seo Moon-joo camp
Known as a spiritual mentor
Lim Doo-jin, director of the Peace Research Institute
Arrested on the spot
Confessed to all espionage activities
Former Ambassador Seo Moon-joo
Participation in espionage activities
They said they confirmed it
Each team barricades
Immediate reporting when installation is complete
1 team
There is currently no vehicle movement
2 teams
Barricade installation completed and waiting
Team 3, setting up barricades
I'll report when it's done
all teams
Strengthen inspection and search
Because the fugitive is armed
Special care required
Our police are responsible for espionage and
He is on the run after being accused of inciting murder.
To arrest Seo Moon-ju
Establishing a joint military and police search headquarters
2,800 police officers, 1,300 military personnel
and block the escape route.
About the whereabouts of Seo Moon-ju
As more information becomes available
Quickly disclose
The citizens
To relieve anxiety
I will do my best
Ha, on a boat
Is it a sin to go out to sea?
Ah, why people
Are you holding them illegally?
For the crime of going out on a boat
You're not here, are you?
October 7th at 5:48
Sergeant Kim Yong-jun's older sister's husband
To Mr. Oh Sang-wook
You deposited 50 million won, right?
About the late Rep. Jang Jun-ik
accused of inciting murder
You are under immediate arrest.
Me?
yes
That's right, right?
The police
Across sea and land routes
A large-scale search was launched, but
Candidate Seo Moon-ju and
What is the whereabouts of bodyguard Baek San-ho?
Not confirmed yet
Meanwhile, surrounding Candidate Seo
From suspicions of a personal relationship with a bodyguard
Up to charges of espionage and instigation of murder
It started popping up one after another...
Ugh
The young woman was too loud
Additional news is
I'll report back to you
It's still okay
this was the plan
I like him
make it a big event
Because it was my intention
A promising presidential candidate
By becoming a murderer and a spy
In front of the entire nation
case of being caught
How were you going to forget me?
I didn't try to forget it
After I broke up with Sanho
It hurt so bad here?
It felt like I was bleeding profusely
'I'm going forward
'I will live and bleed'
I just decided to do it that way.
I'm sorry
I didn't know who the client was
Even so
I wanted to protect Moonju.
I'm sorry too
That audio file, it's because of me.
My mother hacked my laptop
I had Kang Han Na report it.
Even though I know that Sanho is having a hard time,
I couldn't say it
If it weren't for me
I didn't have to go through that.
that night
I found out who I am
A person who has been thirsty for a long time
In fact, I have never
I've never been happy
I've never had what I want
But only one person in the world
just for one night
Can my thirst be satisfied?
So I could accept it.
People's criticism and misunderstanding
I'll pay the price someday
I knew I would pay it
Because I was so happy
Then and now
I can throw it all away
If I can escape safely tonight
let's go
no
I can't accept it
I can't
I am Moonju
Do you know when you first saw it?
Not in the cathedral?
one day
In Iraq...
To the people of Korea
North Koreans are not just anyone
I saw the news
we still
I feel them as brothers
In the distant future we
When I look back on what I have to do today...
‘There is someone like that’
‘To that person’
‘It seems like the sunlight shines differently’
peaceful street
happy family
people who have each other
and
Finish the day safely and drink
for a glass of beer
It was the best day
Mr. Moonju shined in front of people.
I protected you
I've been paid to protect others my whole life.
From that day on
I got to protect the person I care most about.
I am Moonju
I know when you are Mr. Moonju.
peace for all people
hello everyone
Mr. Moonju wants to protect that.
I will only protect Mr. Moonju.
So
Don't stop and run
Revealing the secrets of submarines
Prevent war...
Because I will follow you
we now
Where should I go?
peach?
We...
peach
Shall we eat peaches later?
due to bad weather
Tonight
I think it will be difficult to search any further.
Criminals run away even when it rains
The police can't chase you, right?
Mr. President
Seo Moon-joo is a murderer.
Is this your plan too, Director?
Have you searched everything?
Even the basement and attic?
I looked for it and couldn't find it, Chairman.
He's a kid who hides really well.
If you don't have a mother
Always hiding
He must be sleeping in a corner somewhere
Chairman
I checked the security system and
CCTVs 2, 8, and 11
3 minutes and 30 seconds
There was a record that stopped
Do you know how much he costs?
find
Even if I search to the ends of the earth
mom
Aren't you sleeping?
Yeah
I'm so happy
Yeah?
I always wanted to hide with my mom
Mom too
Should you have come sooner?
No one knows here
Except Junik and me.
No one wants my baby
Like I don't remember
To my door owner
Until I wrote this letter
It took so long
I have a child
The name is Eunseong
I'm 9 years old
I'm waiting
When are you going to tell me?
Let's talk at night
It's going to be a bit of a long story.
no
Talk now
It's now or never I'll never be able to hear it
i have a child
This has been said for a long time
I thought I had to...
I was afraid
Can I live without you?
But I could die
When I thought about it, it became clear.
I should have let you go a long time ago
I'm going to tell everyone in front of everyone
Resign from all public offices
I have to resign from the election too.
And about my mother
I'll reveal the truth
A war caused by submarines
Because I have to stop it
It's all in here
Mother's Secret, Mother's Ledger
If I don't have it
You have to protect yourself with this.
You know what I mean, right?
Is this how it goes?
Moonjuya
Our marriage ended a long time ago.
long before I die
Do you remember?
Whether in 10 years or 20 years
If you get lost
I said I would come to save you
That time is now
I want you...
I came to let you go
You have to be careful
my mother
He's a lot scarier than he looks
There's something terrible inside
thank you for waiting
Where do we go now?
From the courtyard
Until the National Intelligence Service
my mother
More than 30 wives of past leaders
We were close friends
I saw those women holding their first child.
When my mother passed away, I cried with her.
- What?
-Why is it like that?
What, what's going on?
Come in quickly!
Thanks to you, I kill the person I would kill
Save those who need to be saved
status
Looks very critical
Hey, contact me quickly!
To the National Intelligence Service
my mother's file
It doesn't exist
this morning
Lim Doo-jin was poisoned.
At the National Forensic Service
The test results have arrived
Neostigmine bromide
Kim Yong-jun, who murdered Jang Jun-ik, ate
It was a poison-like ingredient.
my daughter-in-law
Did you kill this person too?
Rep. Jang Jun-ik
Who was first suspected of being a spy?
Was dispatched to the National Intelligence Service
It was prosecutor Jang Jun-sang.
Confirmed to be a North Korean manipulation organization
Looking at Chinese phone call history
From your home phone
I found the call log.
And the North Korean front company's
From your Macau bank account...
The company headed by Rep. Jang
Find the details of your remittance
New Republican candidate entered the primary
Rep. Jang Jun-ik's approval rating is
Showing an upward trend every day
Establishment as a leading presidential candidate
It's hardening quickly
Rep. Jang is currently in first place.
Former Governor Hong Seong-oh
While closely pursuing and narrowing the gap,
the rest of the runners
I was left out by a large margin.
After all that worry
I will confess it
My brother...
I think he's a spy
But suddenly
That's what I thought.
Why is someone else in that house?
You may have made a phone call
Have you ever had any doubts?
Are you doubting me now?
Assum Shipping has been operating since 2009.
On a North Korean cargo ship traveling between North and South Korea
We supplied containers
My husband, Chairman Jang Gil-hwan,
He passed away in 2015
The actual chairman is always
It was Chairman Lim Ok-seon.
I am the chairman
Likely to have spoken to North Korea
I think it's enough
Ah!
Prosecutor Jang Jun-sang is outside.
Are you Junsang?
For more information
Let’s check by cross-examination.
There is only one difference between a spy and a patriot.
Because the chairman is a businessman
You know what I mean.
we independently
Operation to eliminate Kim Han-sang
We are preparing
Beating America in this war
How South Korea takes the lead
This is all there is
If the chairman
If you make a contribution here
Chairman
Not a spy, but a patriot
no
You become a hero
The director
Why do you
Do you think you became the head of the National Intelligence Service?
The director was ready.
‘Psychological warfare for a unified Korea’
If you look at the director’s book,
already 20 years ago
Beyond Military Victory
for the public
I'm planning a psychological warfare strategy.
I saw this phrase
'It takes a lot to start a war'
'Like a rocket launch
'Extreme kinetic energy is required'
'About the war
In order to ignite public support'
'One specific incident
'You may need it'
'For example'
'Joan of Arc
'Like burning at the stake'
How do you feel?
Does it fit the current situation?
Let's talk openly
To start a war
Who would you rather burn at the stake?
Is it Seo Moon-ju or Jeon?
Get Seo Moon-joo first.
Then let me help you
Grab Kim Han-sang and cut off his head.
Junsang is outside?
I'll take him with me
- Mom?
- wake up
let's go
Is it your mom who made this call?
Mom...
Did you kill your brother?
You idiot
Son to mother
There's only you
we found out
With Anderson Miller
All transactions of Shiv Holdings
We looked at it together.
I found consistent cash flow
From Yidisha borrowed name account
Enter Shiv Holdings
Back at Shiv Holdings
It goes to an account under a borrowed name in North Korea.
Looking at this flow
North Korea in Yidisha
I'm selling something...
That money flow
Could it have something to do with submarines?
I'm not sure, but it's clear
Yidisha as North Korea's weapon
We're at war with America.
That's Shiv Holdings
I'm mediating
Today we are at Assum Shipping.
I secured the slush fund ledger.
Money coming from hostile countries of the United States
Via Assum Shipping
Apex Starlight
Go into the company
But in Apex Starlight
After learning about it
Representative name
Matthew Sinclair
Coldrain's Treasurer
Cold rain is
Secretary of Defense Eagleton
This is a company where I was an advisor.
From today you
I can't come in here
It's a presidential order.
Yes?
Then someone in America
As an enemy of the United States
Are you talking about exporting weapons?
Stella Young is an American
To hostile and bankrupt countries
Supplying weapons to the United States and North Korea
It's a dark middleman.
Eagleton was a fucking traitor.
This is it! This is the answer
North Korea for 20 years
Despite harsh sanctions
So many weapons
The reason I was able to have it
I was curious too
Why in the world
The war continues
who went through this war
Are you making a profit?
Eagleton has never
I never rejected war
America's enemies use America's weapons
While fighting America
any war
Because it's for his benefit
Meanwhile
Chairman Lim Ok-seon is behind the scenes.
North Korea's weapons manufacturing capabilities
I raised it
Maybe we can make it public.
Secretary of Defense to sell weapons
It has been inciting war all over the world.
Let people know
Hostile countries use American weapons
It was used on American soldiers
When the American people find out
Imagine what would happen
It's more serious than Watergate.
America is in big trouble now!
I need to meet the president.
President Chae Kyung-shin announced this fact
If I could deliver it to the President of the United States
He won't choose war
instructed the police
Evidence of Seo Moon-ju's murder
Let's go over it again from the beginning
Did you do that?
Someone took care of this incident
It's being created
I'm thinking about it
Mr. Midge
Oh, really? I'll go now
Me, candidate
Miji’s arrest warrant was dismissed.
They say you will be released soon.
I will go and get him.
Yes, be careful.
yes
mom is busy
There's a lot to prepare to go far.
So what are you doing?
I'm drawing a picture to give to you.
You look like a deer
Yeah?
how many deer
Do you know if you're good at fighting?
The lion wins and the tiger wins too.
When guarding a doe or baby deer
Mr...
Oh no
Where are you?
Mr. Miji, are you out?
I'm out now and in front of the crosswalk.
Oh, wait a minute.
The car in front was blocked...
Ah!
Then I'll cross the street and wait...
Mr. Midge, Mr. Midge!
Ambassador
I think Miji was in an accident.
But people say
As soon as the accident happened
They said an ambulance came and took them away...
mother
Are you having a hard time talking on the phone?
Mr. Miji, what did you do?
organs rupture
Due to severe intra-abdominal bleeding
If you don't have emergency surgery, you'll die.
I'll hide it from you
Eunseong will bring me within an hour.
Do you have to come on time?
My legs are all crushed
They say it doesn't look good
They'll tell you to cut off your legs first.
If you are even 1 minute late
one by one, one by one
let's go
My mother took my aide.
within an hour
If you don't bring Eunseong with you
My Midge...
Go quickly, Eunseong will take you.
Before my mother's hand reached me
What are you going to do?
I'll take care of this.
Seo Moon-ju is leaving too.
The aide is not important right now.
Dear citizens of Yidisha,
I am with you
we didn't lose the war
Before tomorrow goes
We will win the war
The king of Yidisha
declared war on the United States
The submarine is not at the Yeongpo shipyard.
I left for the Pacific a long time ago
within 24 hours
I will be handed over to Yidisha.
mother
I'm following the submarine.
Something big will happen soon
Americans, listen up
In my country
If you kill one of us
Take revenge on ten people
Why
What happened in our land
It will happen in your land
Have you ever imagined it?
I'm going to Australia
the entire northern hemisphere
Because it might become dangerous
The idea of preventing war
It's better not to do it
we go to war
How can I stop it?
Let's leave quickly
The situation is urgent
Because it seems like it's going back
We found the final solution
I give you just one day
Before the end of tomorrow, America
Begin withdrawal from our land.
Is that video real?
What does final solution mean?
Are you talking about nuclear weapons?
What is the final solution?
Find out quickly
What will I give you?
you will find out soon
Defeat the National Intelligence Service
I need to meet Seo Moon-ju separately.
Let's move quickly
yes
Eunseong, wait a minute.
This necklace is fake
Stealing what Junik bought
I made the same thing because I was jealous.
That person, I never loved
He came to see it every week because it was his child.
I'll be back
coral seed
Be careful driving
According to my source
From Yidisha's secret account
A large amount of money was received several times
To Assum Shipping Paper Company
I went in
We need to freeze that account.
anderson
It's the cost of a submarine.
The submarine will soon head to Yidisha
will be delivered
Soon
The king of Yidisha
Receive the submarine within 24 hours
In the middle of the Pacific Ocean
I was planning on targeting America.
We found the final solution
The final solution is
I'm talking about nuclear missiles.
If you don't receive payment
Kim Han-sang is a submariner.
I won't lead you
How to freeze an account
Can you find it?
Oh, I'm not sure.
Let's give it a try
It's a very difficult situation
I know
I'm really sorry
now you
It's our only hope
So what do you think I'll say?
Now we're all in big trouble
Mr. Moonju, I have some left.
I don't know how much
I'll write it all here
thank you
Safely someday
I wish we could meet
I want to do that too
Mr. Moonju
Sanho, listen carefully.
I am now
I'm going to Chairman Lim Ok-seon.
Where are you going?
mother
I took Mr. Midge.
Eunseong within an hour
He said if I didn't bring him back, I would kill him.
Where are you? I'll go now
no
Sanho has work to do.
I send Eunseong
let's go see the president
What?
In Yidisha
To Assum Shipping account
I think they sent payment for the submarine.
When the submarine is delivered to Yidisha
I don't know what will happen
somehow
explain the situation to the president
To the President of the United States
We need to take action
I have to go after my mother
mother
I'm following the submarine.
Mr. Moonju
This is the best, Sanho.
Someone has to stop my mother
someone to the president
I need to convey a message
Just once
not one person
choose everyone
Only Sanho can do this.
To those who can be trusted
I asked you a favor.
To deliver a message to the Blue House
Just wait a little while
You will be contacted
I'll meet the president right now.
and asap
I will chase after Mr. Moonju.
I have a more difficult mission than this
I did a lot
When I look back at some point
I will be there
I'm confident, so...
Until then, stay safe.
I'm confident too
I know my mother well.
mother can't kill me
Never lose anything
Because you don't
Come quickly
I'll be there soon
What about Eunseong?
Not in Korea
won't come here
Teacher, cut off my leg.
Eunseong's mother
Paternity suit canceled
will never come again
If you wanted children for money
no problem with this
What if it's not about money?
cut off my leg
What my mother wanted
Not Eunseong, not Miji.
I know it's me
I tried cutting off Mr. Miji’s leg.
What joy can there be?
What you want from me
take anything
I came here alone and empty-handed.
Mr. Miji due to insufficient evidence.
You know he was released, right?
Proving my murder charges
It won't be easy
But
I can confess too
My husband Jang Jun-ik
I killed it with my own hands
Then
hidden all over the world
All the money in Mr. Junik’s account is
It will belong to your mother and master.
How do you feel?
teacher
Leave your legs alone
Start with emergency surgery
ride